All 

[Software](javascript:void(0))

[Courses & learning](javascript:void(0))

[Templates](javascript:void(0))

[Creative resources](javascript:void(0))

[All](javascript:void(0))

Top Searches

Main Menu

Go Back

* Browse

**Sumo Group Privacy Policy**

Last modified: May 1, 2024

**Introduction**

Sumo Group Inc. (“ **Company** ,” “ **We,** ” “ **Us** ” or “ **Our** ”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.  

This policy describes the types of information We may collect from you or that you may provide to Us when you visit [https://appsumo.com](https://appsumo.com/) (Our “ **Website** ”) as a guest or when you use or have used Our online or mobile based services (“ **Services** ”) as a user (“ **User** ”). This policy also describes Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.  

This policy applies to information We collect:

* On this Website;
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and Us;
* Through any of Our mobile and desktop applications that you download from Our Website;
* When you interact with Our advertisements and/or applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertisements include links to this policy; 
* When you use Our Services as an active or inactive User. 

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including Our affiliates and subsidiaries); or 
* Any third party (including Our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or through the Website.
* Your posting of information on any of Our public or member forums.  We may provide areas on Our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, your company, communicate with others (such as discussion boards or blogs), review products or restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites; Therefore, this information could be read, collected, and used by others for purposes not disclosed in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you post your email address along with a public restaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other individuals or entities may do with the information you post, so please use caution when posting any personal information on Our public or member forums. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand Our policies and practices regarding your information and how We will treat it. If you do not agree with Our policies and practices, your choice is not to use Our Website or Our Services. By accessing or using this Website or Our Services, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see [Changes to Our Privacy Policy](#changes-to-our-privacy-policy) ). Your continued use of this Website and/or Our Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

**Children Under the Age of 16**

Our Website and Services are not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If We learn We have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, We will delete that information. If you believe We might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact Us at  [support@appsumo.com](mailto:support@appsumo.com)

Residents of certain states under 13, 16, or 18 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their personal information. Please see [Your State Privacy Rights](#your-state-privacy-rights) for more information.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of Our Website and Services, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as first and last name, postal address (if necessary), email address, telephone number and any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("**personal information**");
* That is about you but, without more information, does not directly identify you.  Examples include username, browser type, operating system, IP addresses, and other information collected through cookies related to web traffic to and on Our Website and Services.

_Information You Provide to Us_   

We collect information that you provide directly to Us while using the Website and Services, such as: 

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on Our Website or while using Our Services or signing up to use Our Services. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use Our Website or Our Mobile App(s), subscribing to Our service, posting material, requesting further services, or reporting issues with Our Website or Services.  Examples include your contact information, account and billing information, and social media handles.  
* When creating a profile on our Website and any public forums that we maintain which may require use of your name, creation of an avatar and a biography, if inputted by you.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact Us.
* Your responses to surveys that We might ask you to complete for research purposes.
* Details of transactions you carry out through Our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through Our Website.
* Your search queries on the Website.
* Your use of our artificial intelligence (AI) conversation bot including any information you input through use of the AI bot, which may be subject to additional terms of use and privacy rules of the AI vendor.
* Your use of our messaging boards including currently ‘The Sauce’ ( [https://sauce.appsumo.com](https://sauce.appsumo.com/) ) or ‘Circle’ ( [https://circle.so/](https://circle.so/) ); Note that third-party ‘Circle’ messaging board is independently operated and not controlled by us, see their website for additional information.
* Your submissions through our Website widgets, including ‘GetBeamer’ third-party notification tool used on our Website.
* Your information required to make a purchase on our Website, including your billing information that you provide to us to complete a transaction. Note: we do not collect credit card information directly from you, this information is collected by third-party payment processors, for more information see _Disclosure of Your Personal Information_ below.
* Your support requests directly to us.

     _Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_   

As you navigate through and interact with Our Website, We may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to Our Website, including analytics traffic data (for example by using Google Analytics to obtain how you navigated to Our Website and general analytics including how many users accessed Our Website and from where they were directed to Our Website and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.
* Information regarding your interactions with our Website.

The information We collect automatically is used to provide you with the Services and for statistical purposes that help Us improve Our Website and Services, including by enabling Us to: 

* Estimate Our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing Us to customize Our Website according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Determining whether you are an actual person and not a bot.
* Bug and other error fixes/troubleshooting.
* Recognize you when you return to Our Website.

The technologies We use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of Our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, Our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to Our Website. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  We also utilize a third-party cookie tracking system that allows you to make informed decisions regarding our use of cookies on our Website through cookie banners and pop-ups.  Again, you may also address your browser’s treatment of cookies when you access our Website by navigating to your appropriate browser’s settings.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

We may disclose at Our sole discretion information that is not reasonably linked or linkable to any individual.  

We may disclose personal information that We collect, or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To Our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties We use to support Our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which We disclose it to them.  For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Us is among the data necessarily transferred to the new entity pursuant to such event.
* To third-party payment processors, such as Stripe, Paypal or Klarna if you have transacted on our Website.  (For more information regarding these payment providers’ collection, use and storage of your data please visit: [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy) , or [https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/legalhub/privacy-full) or [https://www.klarna.com/us/privacy/](https://www.klarna.com/us/privacy/) ; please note that We do not maintain these websites and therefore these links may change from time to time).  

_Purpose and Basis of Disclosure_

We may disclose personal information to the above listed entities and/or individuals for the following purposes: 

* To fulfill the purpose for which you provided it.  For example, if you ‘Contact Us’ or use any widgets including chat-bots or other features on Our Website or within Our Mobile Apps that connect to the Website that allow you to input your information.
* To perform services on Our behalf, such as to send Our administrative and promotional emails, fulfill orders, deliver packages, send email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments (by third-party payment providers) for transactions you request, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service.
* We do not share user data with other third-parties, but you may be requested through our Website to share information such as your e-mail address for purposes of fulfilling your purchase or license request and activation of your purchased products/services.  
* For any other purpose disclosed by Us when you provided the information.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply Our Terms of Use ( [https://appsumo.com/terms-of-use/](https://appsumo.com/terms-of-use/) ) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
* If We believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect Our rights, property, or safety, or the rights, property, or safety of Our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

The categories of personal information We may disclose include:

* Personal information such as first and last name, email address, home address, telephone number and any identifying information that you provide to Us using the Website or Services.  
* Credit card information, which We share with third-party payment processing providers including Stripe, PayPal and Klarna.  
* Information that enables Us or Our vendors to deliver Our advertisements to you on third party websites.  For example, We may provide cookie information collected from your interactions with Our Website to Google to enable Google to deliver AppSumo advertisements to you on internet sites or apps that We don’t own, such as on Google’s search browsers or the Facebook app. 

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the Website or Services may then become inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Promotional Offers from the Company.** We may provide Our Users with promotional offers from time to time.   If you are a User and do not wish to have your email address or contact information used by Us to promote Our products and services, you can opt-out of such use by responding to the email indicating that you would like to unsubscribe or by clicking the relevant link in the email footer to unsubscribe from future emails.  You may also make such request by sending Us an email at: [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Complaint%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) .   

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information on websites or apps not owned by Us to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("**NAI**") on the NAI's [website](https://thenai.org/).

Residents of certain states may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your State Privacy Rights](#your-state-privacy-rights) for more information.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change certain personal information such as name, email, phone number and your password by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send Us an email at [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Complaint%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if We believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.     

Residents of certain states may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see [Your State Privacy Rights](#your-state-privacy-rights) below for more information.

**Your State Privacy Rights**

State consumer privacy laws may provide their residents with additional rights regarding Our use of their personal information. 

California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Florida, Indiana, Iowa, Montana, Oregon, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, and Virginia provide (now or in the future) their state residents with rights to:

* Confirm whether We process their personal information.
* Access and delete certain personal information.
* Correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the information's nature processing purpose (excluding Iowa and Utah).
* Data portability.
* Opt-out of personal data processing for:

* targeted advertising (excluding Iowa);
* sales; or 
* profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects (excluding Iowa and Utah).

* Either limit (opt-out of) or require consent to process sensitive personal data. 

The exact scope of these rights may vary by state. To exercise any of these rights please email Us at [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Complaint%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) and state the nature of your request with sufficient detail for Our privacy team to assess the merits of your request.

You may also visit our privacy portal request URL at: [Privacy Request Portal](https://privacysupportservices.com/appsumo)

Nevada provides its residents with a limited right to opt-out of certain personal information sales. We do not currently sell personal information that implicates Nevada’s opt-out rights. However, Nevada residents who wish to contact Us regarding this opt-out right may submit a request by emailing us at [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Complaint%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) .

**Residents of European Economic Area, Switzerland, United Kingdom**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), Switzerland or United Kingdom, you have certain additional rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data at the end of this privacy policy.

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. All information you provide to Us is stored on Our secure servers behind firewalls. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where We have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of Our Website or Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although We do Our best to protect your personal information, We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to Our Website or through Our Services. Although We employ industry standard security mechanisms to protect your data and use only reputable third-party service providers (including payment processors), any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for your circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website or while using Our Services.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is Our policy to post any changes We make to Our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If We make material changes to how We treat Users' personal information, We will notify you by sending an email to the primary email address specified in your account and through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the privacy policy. You are responsible for ensuring We have an up-to-date, active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting Our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes prior to your access of Our Website or use of Our Services.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and Our privacy practices, contact Us at: 

Sumo Group, Inc. (dba “AppSumo”) 1305 E. 6th Street #3 Austin, TX 78702

Toll-Free: (833) 833-1961

To register a complaint or concern, please submit a request to initiate a complaint by emailing Us at [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Complaint%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) with the heading/title “Privacy Complaint” and providing Us with sufficient detail regarding the nature of your complaint and the date/time of any events leading up to your complaint.  We may ask you to verify your complaint and identity by providing appropriate information to substantiate your identity and the facts giving rise to your complaint.

**GDPR EEA Notice:**

The terms and provisions in this Section only apply to EEA, Switzerland/UK Residents and only to the extent that we are subject to the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). If there is any conflict between the GDPR Terms and the rest of this Privacy Policy, the GDPR Terms shall control with respect to EEA Residents (and only to the extent that we are subject to GDPR). Our identity and contact information is as follows:

Address:

Sumo Group, Inc., a Delaware corporation d/b/a AppSumo 1305 E. 6th St. Suite 3 Austin, TX 78702

Email: support@appsumo.com

We rely on the following legal grounds to process your personal information:

* **Consent.**  We may use your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy subject to your consent. To withdraw your consent, please contact us at [EMAIL HERE](mailto:appsumo1@bearflagservices.zohodesk.com?subject=Privacy%20Notice%20Inquiry%20(GDPR)%20(AppSumo-Sumo%20Group)) .

* **Performance of a contract.**  We may need to collect and use your personal information, as applicable, to perform our contractual obligations.

* **Legitimate Interests.**  We may use your personal information for our legitimate interests to provide our products, our partners’ products, and our services and to improve our services and the content on the Website. We may use technical information as described in this Privacy Policy and use personal information for our marketing purposes consistent with our legitimate interests and any choices that we offer or consents that may be required under applicable law.

* **Legal Compliance.**  We may collect and use your information in connection with legal obligations to which we are subject. These legal obligations include, but are not limited to, any and all applicable (i) federal, state, or local laws, rules, or regulations, (ii) court orders, or (iii) consent decrees.

We may use information that we collect about you, including personal information, to:

* **Provide Products and Services.**  We will use your information to provide our products, our partner’s products, and our services to you; to respond to your inquiries; and for other customer service and support purposes. We use the payment information you provide to us in order to alert you of past, current, and upcoming charges, to allow us to present the purchase history to you, and to perform internal finance processes, such as looking the status of a credit card charge. In the event of a credit card dispute, we also share account information with your bank to verify the legitimacy of a charge.

* **Understand and improve our products.**  We will perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, our partner’s products, our services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others. We do this to help make our products better and to develop new products.
* **Communicate with you.**

* **Service related communications.**  We may send you service and administrative emails to ensure the products or services are working properly. These messages are considered part of the service and you may not opt out of these messages.

* **Promotional.**  Subject to your opt-out preference, we may send you emails about new product features or other news about AppSumo or on topics we think would be relevant to you. You may opt out of receiving these communications at any time by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the applicable email or sending us a request at support@appsumo.com.

* **Responding to your requests.**  We will also use your information to respond to your questions or comments.

* **Administrative.**  We may contact you to inform you about changes in our services, our service offering and other important service related notices, such as changes to the Privacy Policy or about security or fraud notices.

* **Advertising.**  Subject to your opt-out preferences, we may develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our services and other sites.

* **Protecting Rights and Interests.**  We will use your information to protect our rights and interests as well as the rights and interests of our users and any other person, as well as to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service,

* **Legal Compliance.**  We may use your information to comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including informal requests from law enforcement or other governmental authorities

* **Other.**  We also may use your information to manage our business or perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection subject to your consent. Please read all online agreements carefully before accepting them.

**SMS abandoned cart disclosure:**

  The website uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS.

**Third-party data sharing:**

  The above excludes text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties.

Part of the Sumo family  
with [TidyCal](https://tidycal.com/), [FiveTaco](https://fivetaco.com/), and [SendFox](https://sendfox.com/).

#### Account

#### AppSumo

#### Sell

#### Learn
